

# **NGUYEN THE HIEP**

**FE REACTJS** 

### **Profile**

Full name: Nguyen The Hiep

birth: 22/8/1998

I have a lot of experience developing software for some companies. I am reliable, adaptable to the working environment, and flexible enough to handle problems in many situations. I am completely self-sufficient in my studies. I like to explore new tech for my work.

## **Education History**

Bachelor in IT Sep 2016 - Jul 2021

Hanoi University of Industry

### <u>Languages</u>

#### English

- Good logical and algorithmic thinking skills, analysis, and problem-solving.
- Capable of reading and comprehending specialized English.

### **Skills**

- Team Working Skill
- Time Management Skill
- · Critical Thinking Skill
- Analyzing & Problem Solving Skill
- Communication Skill

## Work Experience

- Intern FPTS, Oct 2020 - Mar 2021
  - · Exploring cloud computing
  - · Database of learning queries
- Intern Monstarlab, Nov 2021 - May 2022
- Frame work: Nestjs
- Language: Typescript, Javascript, HTML, CSS
- Database: Mysql
- Support: git, docker
- · demo:

https://gitlab.com/te2042/demonestjs/-/tree/main/serve

# **Contact Info**

- 038.613.2323
- nguyenthehiep3232@gmail.com
- thon 2, Phuong Cach, Quoc Oai, Ha Noi